Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 17
I couldn't get hold of you all night.
What in the world are you doing?
Where are you?...Huh??
How about Mom? Are you with her?
Where are you coming from?
Why are you like this? Are you okay?
I'm asking why you're like this...How about Mom?
You said you went out with her.
Mom ran away, Unni.
What?
What did you say?
Let's go into your room.
I did it because I felt sorry for Dad.
I felt so sorry because I couldn't kick Mom out.
I put Ahjussi Jang in front of Dad
and I hid behind that action.
I held Mom's hand so tightly.
Because I didn't want to lose Mom.
I went as far to go looking for him but it ended like this.
Mom....and you......
You two women.....
What are they to me?
What are they?
What are they really?
What are they that you can't let go of them?
I'm asking you...
If I ask, you should answer.
What's the reason you can't let go of Mom and me?
If I were you, I would've let us go more than a dozen times already.
No matter how much you are of another world, someone I can't understand
and even though you can't distinguish the thing in front of you, if it's a puppy or a wolf.
Even if you were born with a fate to love a wolf
even knowing Mom did it
without even uttering a word to me, smiling.
You held on to me completely exhausted from crying that Mom ran away.
You can't do this.
I can't do this?
Then, Mom can?
Who's more ridiculous?
Is it me?
It's me.
This won't do, Hyo Seon. This simply won’t do.
Because Mom and I have committed so many wrongdoings to you, to Dad and to this household...
I was determined to live a life just worshipping at your feet.
But, this won't do.
Please kick me out, Hyo Seon.
Where would you go? Sit down.
Where are you going?
Let go.
Let go! Please let go of me, Hyo Seon.
Please let go of me.
No, you can't.
Let go!
No! You can't!
I don't want to! I hate you!
I hate everything! It's all disgusting!
I told you to let go!
How could you not know?
How could you not know a person's feelings, Unni?!
You didn't know?
You and Mom...
You're both sick
You're sick humans.
You've lived here for eight years, but how it's possible...
How can you turn all that time into nothing?
You and me how can you make us become like we have no relationship.
Between Mom and Dad...
Is Joon Soo.
That means that between you and I, we have Joon Soo as well.
But, how can you ask me to kick you out?
If you are not sick,
how can you say something like that?
I really think...
I'm going to go insane because of you, Goo Hyo Seon.
Goo Eun Jo.
I think I'm going to go insane too.
Mom...
Bring her back.
I think I'm going insane.
Hyo Seon's hands...
And Hyo Seon's forehead,
Like a hot iron rod, were hot.
Should I also pluck out all of the sharpened claws of mine both in my hands and feet
and just hug this feverishly hot child?
So if I also become hot like her
would this child I do not understand, will I be able to understand her?
Even though my mom ran away, I was not schocked at all by that.
It was absolutely nothing compared to the shock given to that child Hyo Seon.
I'll ask this of you.
I don't think my mom is seeing Ahjussi again.
We never know so just in case go meet Ahjussi once.
Ask where she went, or if she contacted him by any chance.
Since she didn't take any money with her when she left,
She might've contacted Ahjussi Jang for some help.
I got it. Don't worry.
I'll be back.
Is Hyo Seon alright?
Is her fever down?
It went down a little, but she still feels hot.
Hyo Seon's grandfather will come.
Do you want to go see her for a while?
I have to take Joon Soo to kindergarten.
Since I woke him up late this morning, he missed the school bus.
And what else?
What else? Tell me what else.
Because you were sticking to her side like gum,
she probably couldn't clear up her thoughts.
She must have needed this time to herself.
And?
As soon as she clears up her thoughts, I'm sure she'll defintely come back.
Now get some sleep until your grandfather comes.
Be a good girl.
Goo Joon Soo, raise your head.
I said to raise your head. You have to see what's in front of you.
Where did Mom go?
I told you she had some business to do.
When is she coming?
I don't know.
In no time. Soon.
Do you know SNSD?
What?
What about T-ara?
And U-Kiss?
What are you talking about?
♪ Do I really seem that easy to you, hey?!♪
♪ I used to be nice, soft and tender but if I keep going crazy like this ♪
♪ Because of you, I’m turning myself into something strong ♪
♪ I have put a spell again on a puppet that looks like you ♪
♪ I order you to break up with her. Tear away from her ♪
You don't know this?
What is that?
♪ Bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep. Ah! ♪
♪ Bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep. Ah! Ah! ♪
You don't know this either?
Forget it. Mom knows it all.
What did you say? Mom knows all of that?
Forget it, Evil Witch! Don't talk to me!
Why there aren't any snacks left?! What's this?
Ah, I'll prepare more quickly and I'll bring them to you.
Yes, I'll make them quickly, so please wait.
Come here my pretty.
- It's not like we see each other only once or something
- Don't be like that
Are you trying to play coy because you're pretty or what!
Don't let her be!
Please stop that!
- Let go. Let go of me.
- Come here. Come here, wench.
Why are you acting like this?!
Don't interfere!
- Hello? There is...
Hey, who are you calling and saying hello?
- Let go, you punk!
- Calm down.
- Get your hands off her!
- And who are you?!
Hit him, Kang Sook. I said get your hands off me!
Let go! In whose presence do you dare! Go away! Go away I said!
Hey! Hey! Who do you think you are?! Hey, hey!
Hey, why are you being like this?
Crazy man, just leave! What else do you want me to do for you to leave?
Don't look over there. Look at me instead.
Let's go outside for a little while.
Ahjussi says that he hasn't seen her after that morning.
All right.
Noona, I'll stay with Ahjussi tonight and go back tomorrow. It's already late.
Okay then. Ah, right. Jeong Woo...
Goo Joon Soo.
If Mom comes late because she's busy, I'll do that for you.
I can go for you. To your kindergarten.
I don't want you to! You're ugly! I'm going to ask Little Noona to go as my partner!
But, Little Noona is still sick.
If Little Noona is still sick by then, I said I'll do it for you.
You're lying!
I'm not lying.
You don't even know how to do it!
I know how.
Don't lie, Evil Witch!
Come over here.
These are records of alcohol that your father had recorded himself
and translations of old texts (old texts were in Chinese traditional characters).
I always wanted to sort all this out and save it on the computer.
Because I might not have enough time, my heart feels rushed.
I might not be able to do it, so come and watch.
Look, if you don't like what I've sorted out, you can sort it out again.
Leave it and go.
I'll take care of it, so leave it and go.
I have to use the computer.
As I was organizing I found files not just on alcohol
but also personal notes were found too.
Anyway, I think you or Hyo Seon should wrap it up.
January, 2003, I've received my third gift
♪ Bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep. Ah! ♪
♪ Bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep. Ah! Ah! ♪
♪ Bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep. Ah! Ah!♪
♪ Bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep. Ah! ♪
♪ Bo peep bo peep. Ah! ♪
♪ Bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep bo peep. Ah! Ah! ♪
There's nothing funnier.
In this situation, I've been told to dance something cute.
My mom is really...
She's truly a ridiculous woman.
Let's go.
Noona called and told me to give Joon Soo's little noona some food.
Let's go. Grandmother has made rice porridge and put it out for you already.
Are you going to continue to not listen?
What are you doing here sitting blankly?
I'm waiting.
I'm going to wait.
Can I tell you something?
Ahjumma... will come back.
She did the same thing before.
She would leave somewhere for a while without saying a word,
but she always came back.
If she was going to run away forever,
Ahjumma wouldn't have left neither Noona nor Joon Soo behind.
She would've come back and taken them with her.
So are you saying that they'll all run away together?
That's what would've happened,
but I don't think Noona Eun Jo will leave this place.
Then, that means Ahjumma will have to live here too.
Even if Joon Soo's little noona were to kick her out,
if Noona Eun Jo is here, then Ahjumma will remain too.
Believe what I say and please get up.
When Ahjumma comes back to pick up Noona Eun Jo and Joon Soo and tries to run away with them,
If you want to hold them back with all your strength, will you be able to make it in such state?
Mom
This phone is turned off at the moment. Please leave a message after the beep.
Incoming call
054-123-4567
Hello?
Mom?
For your whole life, you sang saying that if I didn't exist you'd be happy.
Mom!
I'm afraid so.
Mom, where are you? Where are you right now?
I'll go to you right away. Tell me where you are, Mom!
When you tried to run away, I should've pretended not to know and let you leave.
Exchanging numbers
and meet once or twice a year.
It would've been nice if we were cordial like that.
Why is it that I held onto you having you see things that you shouldn't be exposed to.
Mom, let's meet and talk. Let's talk face-to-face.
Hyo Seon is half dead and Joon Soo keeps asking for you.
Why are you being like this?
Mom. If you run away like this, will it make everything better?
If Mom just runs away, are you saying that it doesn't matter what happens to the others?
Even if you were to leave, it shouldn't be this way. Where are you?
I'll go to you right away so tell me where you are!
I'm contemplating whether I should go or not.
Once I reach a decision, I'll let you know as soon as possible.
I haven't decided anything yet.
Mom. Mom!
The number you have called does not exist.
It says that it's an untraceable number. What does that mean?
It's probably a public phone. Give me your phone.
She must be around Pohang area. Let's look into it.
This looks like a public phone number.
Could you tell us the exact location?
If it's not the exact location, then somewhere close to the vicinity.
What? I can go alone. You're not even feeling well.
There's no use thinking for the duration of our ride there.
You should nap for a little while.
I've contacted your friend Jeong Woo too,
so no matter who arrives first, we'll be able to find her.
We have to find her for Hyo Seon.
I know.
Even if we have to knock on all the doors of every single house in the vicinity, we'll look for her.
We will find her.
Leave me the car and go home. I'll go alone.
Go and stay with Hyo Seon.
Grandmother and Ahjumma are home, so don't worry.
I said go and stay with her!
Don't get so worked up and just close your eyes.
I told you to go stay with Hyo Seon!
What are you doing?
I asked what you are doing!
I don't have anything else to reveal to you.
Because I've told you everything, I feel at ease.
In the past, even though I worried and felt sorry for you,
I couldn't do anything I wanted because I was hiding something.
It's okay now.
No matter what you think of me or how much you dislike me...
From now on, I'm going to allow myself to worry about you. I'll do that.
So boldly?
That's right. I've wanted to be this bold for a long time.
Because I couldn't, I felt like I was going to die.
So don't say anything to me,
So while I'm even putting my life on the line to swear loyalty, accept me.
Let's go find your mom.
Now that we've driven all around,
I think it'd be better to get out and take a walk while looking out for her carefully.
Little Noona, you should rest in the car.
Excuse me.
Where is the public pay phone that people use a lot around here?
According to the navigation system, we're near Kyung Jae city.
How long will it take for you to get here?
Why will it take that long?
I understand. Please come soon.
I don't think we'll be able to take the car.
Then, what are we supposed to do?!
When those people get here, we'll leave the car with them and take the bus.
I'm really going insane!
That guy Jeong Woo and Hyo Seon arrived just now. They're already looking for her everywhere.
How can you smile?
I guess I want to keep talking to you.
There's so much we haven't talked about all this time.
Because there is nothing I need to hide anymore, I feel like I'm going to burst out talking.
Even though this is a very serious situation where we're trying to find your mom.
I keep wanting to say things that have nothing to do with this.
I think they're about to pour out of me. Will you listen?
- What's wrong with you? What are you doing?
- Come here.
I said to come here.
Why are you doing this?!
Lean. It'll be hard otherwise.
You're already getting into a huff, how come you haven't changed.at all?
When we first saw each other after 8 years,
I wondered how you could look at me with that glare for a while.
It was rude.
Stop it. I don't want to hear this. I won't hear you!
Lean. Huh? Listen to me.
I'm telling you to lean on something.
I can't stand it. It makes me uneasy seeing you jumping up and down by yourself.
I think the place, where we were before near the front entrance of the market,
It looks like a spot where people are bound to pass some time or other.
so I think it'll be better if we stay there and wait.
Let's go back there. And before we leave, we can eat a bit.
I have no appetite.
If I don't feed Joon Soo's little noona some food, I'll be in big trouble with Noona Eun Jo.
Follow me.
Welcome!
What would you like? Liquor?
Not liquor. Please give us some food.
The pollack soup is good.
We'll take that. Please give us some.
Is that okay with you?
Anyway, everything tastes the same to me.
Please give me whatever takes you the least time to prepare.
Then, should I give you soup with rice?
Is that the quickest thing to make?
Then, we'll take soup with rice.
Two soups with rice at the table over there, Kang Sook.
Kang Sook, what are you doing?
Lower your voice!
Why? What's wrong?
Give them their food slowly. Please give them a lot.
Give them a lot so that they remain seated and eat for a very long time.
Thank you.
Mom! Did Ahjumma leave?
No. Oh, y-yeah!
Ahjumma left her wallet here. All of her money's inside.
Where did she go? I'll bring it to her.
♫  Leaving behind the time  ♫
♫  which was buried in my heart  ♫
♫  I said I longed for you  ♫
♫  and waited for you  ♫
♫  Even my memory which turned away  ♫
♫  doesn't know that I longed for you  ♫
♫  Looking only in this direction  ♫
♫  my two eyes  ♫
♫  can't say they waited for you  ♫
♫  I can't say I'm coming back  ♫
♫  Will you who knows everything about me  ♫
♫  who cannot forget me  ♫
♫  return to me?  ♫
♫  If there are tens of thousand who will just love you  ♫
♫  If I can always look at you  ♫
♫  The day I return to your side again  ♫
♫  will come again  ♫
Han Jeong Woo
We have found Ahjumma
How could you really do this?!
Hyo Seon. Listen to what I have to say.
Even if you forcibly drag me away with that kid.
I'll leave again.
And do you think I'll let you?
No matter what I have to do, I'll leave again.
Why?
So, just leave for now.
Why?!
- Hyo Seon.
- Why?
This woman named Song Kang Sook...
For the first time since I was born,
I've realized what I've done that keeps me from holding my head up at the age of 50.
So that's why...
Since I'm out of the house, I can hold my head up.
Then lower your head and live in front of me.
That was to be your punishment!
Leave.
Or else I'll be sure to disappear and die.
What did you say?
Disappear and die?
Yeah. Disappear and die.
Go home and ask Eun Jo.
How I lived in the past.
What kind of atrocities I committed without batting an eyelid.
Ask her.
So, just leave.
Because when I'm ready to return home, I will.
I said to leave immediately.
Then promise me.
That you'll come.
If you promise me that you'll come back whenever it's time...
I'll leave.
You won't promise me?
Whenever it's the correct time, I'll go back.
And promise me another thing.
That you won't go anywhere else
and that you'll stay here at your old friend's house.
Alright.
I promise it so leave immediately.
Joon Soo keeps asking for you.
Why is a wench like you worrying about Joon Soo?
When I'm his mother. Are you even close to what I am?
What is this?
Did you sleep well?
Where are we? When did we get here?
I wanted to let you sleep for just 10 minutes more so I begged the ahjussi,
but 30 minutes passed instead.
What did you say?
Hyo Seon found your mom.
We were going to switch buses from here to get there.
But, we don't need to.
What did you say?
And so they decided to wait for her at home.
They believed what she said? They believed my mom's words?!
Is she a fool?!
Stop lying. You know, Ahjumma!
Does it even make sense that you don't know?
Ahjumma, you're the one who sent my mom somewhere else!
Where did you send her to? Please tell me, Ahjumma!
I told you that's not the case.
After they came and left, she came right back and packed all her stuff and went out right away!
Then you should have held onto her, Ahjumma!
Hey, I also run a business here.
Then I should leave the business empty and only chase your mother's tail?!
This...this... even from when she was little had not even a chick's sleepy seed's worth of respect. You dare behave in this way in front of an adult?
Hey, did you even greet me today? You know me!
When you were born I even cut your umbilical cord...
Ahjumma! I asked to tell me where my mom went!
Oh, I'm really going crazy.
Hey, if you come at me and behave like this, I wouldn't tell you even if I knew!
How in the world am I supposed to tell a kid what she wants to know...
When it's something that I don't even know?!
What a brat. You're really a disrespectful one.
Hey, leave you brat! I can't bear the sight of you.
Hey! You little...
Hey! How come you...
Hey, get out. Get out!
Don't even think about coming back here!
Open the door, Ahjumma!
Ahjumma, how can you do this?!
How can you do this after my mom abandoned me, Ahjumma?!
Did you encourage her to abandon me?
Open the door, Ahjumma!
Let go.
I said to open the door!
Open the door. Let go! I said let go of me.
I said let go.
Let go.
I said let go of me.
She told me that she hasn't thought once about abandoning me...
But, she abandoned me in the end.
Even if I die, you acted as if you'd never leave. So stubborn.
Just because she was having a hard time...
she abandoned me.
When I was young,
some sturdy men grabbed me away from my mom's hands and dragged me into a car.
My mom was running after us crying and begging them not to take me.
And while I was in the car being taken away, I thought
"Oh, my mom is running when she shouldn't."
You shouldn't be running, but you are running.
So that's how I was separated from my mom and ended up abandoning her before I knew it.
While I was growing up, no one would let me see her.
♫  I'm secretly smiling  ♫
One day my mom came looking for me at the house I was living at with my hyungs, because she wanted to see me.
Hyeong wanting to lose my mom, made her run.
If he'd just let me see her once,
she wouldn't have had to pass away like that.
♫  I walk this street again  ♫
I'll find her for you. Your mom.
I'll find her for you.
So don't worry.
♫  In your name when tears appear  ♫
♫  I can't bear it  ♫
♫  So I can't laugh  ♫
♫  I call out your name again  ♫
Mom. I miss you.
Mom.
- When is Mom going to come?
- Joon Soo. Don't cry please.
I went to go see Mom
and her friend was so sick.
As soon as her friend gets better, she said she'd come back.
Mom!
Mom...
You bratty little punk.
You bad little punk.
You bratty and beautiful little punk.
You you you you bratty little punk! Punk punk punk punk punk!
You bratty little punk! Punk punk punk punk punk!
You beautiful, bad little punk!
You bad little punk!
Aren't you tired?
Give him to me.
It's okay. He's falling asleep.
Our puppy is sleeping so peacefully.
Our puppy, our beautiful little punk.
He's sleeping so peacefully.
Our puppy... sleep tight.
When you were young and couldn't fall asleep,
did he do the same thing for you like he did for Joon Soo?
What are you talking about?
Dad...
You beautiful punk.
You bratty punk.
You bratty and beautiful little puppy.
What did you just say?
You beautiful punk. You bratty punk.
You bratty and beautiful little puppy.
No, not that.
You said Dad?
Did you say Dad?
Does it feel awkward?
Why is this the first time I'm hearing you say that?
You should have said it earlier.
Why did you act like such a selfish brat?
Hyo Seon.
Tell me.
What if Mom...
if she doesn't keep the promise she made with you,
and doesn't ever come back.
What do you think it'll be like?
She's not coming back?
That's not what I said.
I said "if".
Don't do that.
Don't ask that question.
Please ask me why I believe that Mom is going to return.
Why?
Mom said she couldn't hold her head up.
What did you say?
This woman named Song Kang Sook...
For the first time since I was born,
I've realized what I've done that keeps me from holding my head up.
Mom said that she couldn't hold her head up high?
But abandoning Joon Soo is something
that'll make her even more ashamed to hold her head up.
And also...
It's because I think
Mom feels like me
that I don't want to spit on those years.
You feel like that too.
No matter how hard these past 8 years have been,
no matter how much you disliked me,
wasn't Dad your strength and support?
So, no matter how shitty the things we had experienced were.
you spitting on all of that time that passed,
is the same as spitting on Dad as well.
And the same goes for Mom too.
Even though it's really hard for me to believe,
she said Mom has learned something called shame.
While I wasn't paying attention, Hyo Seon had grown
from a naive girl who could get everything with her silliness and cuteness
to a mature adult who could express her years.
I just remained the same girl who had her claws out.
Who are you?
You're the child of the owner of that restaurant, right?
I asked who you were.
Right. You must be curious about who I am, right?
Are you a kidnapper?
That's not it.
I just wanted to know if you could relay a message to your mother's friend who is staying at your house now.
My mom's friend?
She's not staying at my house right now.
Really? Then, I guess it's not possible.
Okay. I'm sorry for taking some of your time when you're on your way to school.
But, what did you want to tell her?
You said she wasn't staying here.
If she's not there, there's nothing that can be done.
Go.
Mom!
Yes, hello?
Who did you say you were?
Director Park?
Yes.
Someone must have come looking for you.
A certain ahjussi did.
Jeong Woo, we need to talk.
Eun Jo has just left the research lab and is heading here right now,
but stop her along the way and keep her away so that she can't come to the winery.
What's going on?
I don't have time to explain.
Take her somewhere else and stay with her until late afternoon.
Hurry.
Yes, this is Hong Gi Hoon.
I'm booting it now.
Please tell me a little more about the documents you've sent me.
I've got a call that the elders of Dae Seong True Winemakers are on their way over here right now.
By any chance, does this have anything to do with it?
Where are we going right now?
You said that you wanted to go somewhere with me. There's this really killer place.
I have to go to the winery now.
I have to take Hyo Seon to the hospital to see why she can't taste anything,
I have to find Mom and look after Joon Soo as well.
I don't know what this is about, but stop fooling around and go back to the winery.
Seonbae Hong is at the winery.
Grandmother and Ahjumma can look after Joon Soo.
And Joon Soo's little noona went to give an interview for a magazine.
And your mom said she'd come back so all we have to do is wait.
Jeong Woo.
I have something I have to tell you!
I don't have any other intention, but I'm sick.
It seems I don't have much time left.
Before I leave, I didn't want to leave such untied ends behind.
Hongju Brewery don't know if they don't.
The fact that they know is very worrisome.
I understand.
I'll discuss this with the two daughters of the family and meet with you all again.
But...
I'd like to know about the terms and conditions offered to you
for the transfer of your shares to Hong Joo Ga.
I'll take the liberty of addressing you all.
Dae Seong True Winemakers is not a company that can be handed over to scum like Hong Joo Ga.
I don't know what conditions Hong Joo Ga offered you all but...
Shut your mouth. Aren't you just an employee here?
Yes I am, but Elder-
We came here to meet with the two daughters of this household.
I did not come to report to you.
We'd better come back tomorrow.
Elders.
Hyo Seon and Eun Jo are still shocked by the President's sudden death.
The company and factory have had bad setbacks and
the mother of the two children has even left their house, so they're emotionally and physically exhausted.
If Hyo Seon and Eun Jo hear what you elders have to say,
I don't think they'll have energy left to hold on much longer
Please tell me the conditions offered by Hong Joo Ga.
And also, please give us some more time
so that I can both protect Daeseong True Winemakers
while not burdening the elders. There will definitely be a way.
As you know the orders have been overflowing from not only domestically but from overseas.
That's enough. We won't listen anymore.
We'll come back tomorrow.
From Park Ki Man - To Hong Gi Hoon: Please read this.
This is regarding Dae Seong True Winemakers...
About Daeseong True Winemakers.hwp
Jeong Woo.
I don't even have the energy to get angry. Why are you doing this?
You know that I'm not in a situation where I can relax and play around in a place like this!
Why are you acting like this too when you already know?!
What date is it today?
Do you know what date is today?
I didn't do this because I wanted to celebrate my birthday,
but still, I thought you'd make some seaweed soup for me.
Don't be like that, stop frowning. Relax your face.
For just one day, what I wanted Noona is...
for you to stop thinking about the winery, your household problems, you mom, and to get rid you of all your worries.
Have you ever rested?
You haven't, right?
Noona, you resting will be my birthday present.
You don't want to give me this present?
You won't give me this?
Are you Director Park?
I'm not anymore, but it's fine if you call me that.
Please sit down.
We didn't have to meet in person.
Thank you for taking the time to see me.
Are you curious about my intentions?
To be honest, that's right I am.
The reason you gave me those documents.
I had fallen victim to many things, so hoped that you would take on my rage.
Look here, I'll be honest. That is part of it. No, it's probably most of it.
I have a heart to be furious, but it's not manly.
And I had taken a lot of benefits all this time
so even with that I can live quietly.
But when a person gets sick and finds out he's dying soon,
it's the right thing to believe in the sincerity of the words said by those who are about to die.
And above all
whether my intentions are pure or tainted
What's wrong is still wrong, isn't that so?
Those documents whichever way you use them, it's fine.
Whether you expose them to the world or you put them as a condition to save Daeseong True Winemakers
and cut a deal with the Hongju Family.
If we need to submit all those documents to the prosecutor's office
and report Hongju Family, then you General Director would be investigated.
You think it'll be just an investigation? I'll probably wear a pair of handcuffs.
I'm prepared for what's to come.
But, you're sick.
Those are my circumstances and I'll deal with them on my own.
♫  In the depth of my heart  ♫
♫  When loneliness comes again  ♫
♫  I also don't know again what you intend  ♫
♫  Without saying anything, smile again  ♫
Noona!
♫  More than saying you loved me  ♫
Buy this for me.
Stop fooling around.
This one looks like you.
How does this look like me?
And you look like this one.
♫  I said I liked you so much  ♫
You don't think it looks like you?
♫  Today you must tell me  ♫
♫  My love, will you run to me?  ♫
Don't do it.
Please, it's for my birthday.
You're going to keep fooling around?
♫  I too unconsciously am waiting for you  ♫
♫  Today for me is the day for your sake  ♫
♫  I am going to love you this way  ♫
Let's go.
Take it off.
Go in.
Eun Jo.
What's going on here?
That person is crazy.
Why does he call me like that?
Come over here.
Did he forgot the sins he committed?
Why does he call me like that?
I said come here.
He's smiling.
He's definitely crazy.
And I'm definitely crazy too.
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt.  ♫